

PROFILE

I'm Junita, a results-driven sales professional with a focus exceptional customer service and outstanding sales performance. Experienced in surpassing targets, building loyal relationships, contributing to effective sales strategies. With strong sales, negotiation, and problem-solving skills, I am confident in driving sales and contributing to organizational success.

CONTACT

MOBILE NUMBERS: +977-9840364606 +977-9810327867

EMAIL: junitakhati@gmail.com

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Traveling
- Cooking and Baking
- Socializing
- Community Events

LANGUAGES

- Nepali (95%)
- English (75%)
- Hindi (80%)

JUNITA SUNAR

Sales Girl

EDUCATION

Shree Mahesh dharma secondary school

2014 - 2015

I have successfully completed my SLC examination with a second division, securing 50 Percent marks.

Shree Mahesh dharma secondary school

2015 - 2018

I have successfully completed my NEB examination with 45 Percent.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Namo Nama Jewellers, Sales Girl (2022-Working)

Exceeded sales targets, drove revenue growth at Namo Nama Jewellers. Known for exceptional customer service, loyalty building, and memorable shopping experiences. Implemented effective sales strategies, increased footfall, and optimized inventory for customer satisfaction and sales opportunities.

Nirjara beauty parlour, Beautician (2021-2022)

Built strong client rapport, fostering trust and loyalty for repeat business and referrals. Delivered exceptional beauty treatments, exceeding customer expectations. Commended for outstanding service, boosting customer satisfaction ratings.

Sanakishan sahakari secondary school, Teacher (2020-2021)

I have one year of teaching experience in the field of education, specifically for classes ranging from first grade to fifth grade.

SKILLS

- 1. Customer Service
- Sales and Upselling
- 3. Communication
- 4. Time Management
- 5. Problem Solving
- 6. Attention to Detail
- 7. Basic knowledge of ms-office (ms-word, ms-powerpoint, excel etc.)